Next, we'll fix the behavior of the Order button.
続いて 「 Order 」ボタンの 動作を修正します
Once I change the quantity to something like six, if I hit the Order button,
一度 数量を変えてみます ６ にして「 Order 」ボタンを押すと―
the price should update to $30.
料金が $30 に更新されるはずです
However, when I click the Order button,
しかし 「 Order 」ボタンを押すと―
it always changes the quantity back to five and the price to $25.
いつも 数量が５に戻って 料金も $25 になってしまいます
So this behavior is incorrect.
この動作は間違っていますね
To test your understanding of everything we've learned so
今までに学んできたことに対する 理解度を試すために―
far, I want you to go ahead and fix this bug on your own.
自分自身でこのバグを修正してください
I'm confident that you can do it.
きっとできると思いますよ
This is a very common occurrence during app development.
こういうことはアプリ開発の期間中に とてもよく起こることです
You build out more functionality of your app, like this quantity picker, but
この数量ピッカーボタンの様に 機能を増やすと―
then it can have ripple effects on the rest of your app.
残りの部分に波及することがあります
And it may break something, like this Order button.
そして この「 Order 」ボタンの様に 破たんが起きるかもしれません
So you have to just go back and fix that later.
そうなったら 前に戻って 修正する以外に道はありません
Once you've completed this task, this is what the app should look like.
このタスクを完了したら アプリはこの様になるはずです
If I increase the quantity to something like six, and
例えば 数量を 6 に増やして―
I hit the Order button, then the price changes to $30, which is correct.
「 Order 」ボタンを押すと 料金はちゃんと $30 に変わります
To help you tackle this problem,
この問題に取り組む時のヒントとして―
first identify all the things that are wrong with the current state of the app.
まず 現段階のアプリで 不具合部分を全て見つけます
You can look at it on your device, and so
デバイス上で確認できますので―
it will be easier than looking at this screenshot.
このスクリーンショットを 見つめるよりも簡単でしょう
This screenshot shows setting the quantity to six and
このスクリーンショットが示しているのは 数量を 6 に設定することと―
then hitting the Order button and seeing the result on the screen.
「 Order 」ボタンを押した時に 表示される結果です
I want you to describe in words the gap between what we have now and
現状と希望する状態の違いを―
what we want.
言葉で説明してください
Be as detailed as possible by writing your answer in this box.
出来るだけ詳細を この四角の中に書き入れてください
The more specific you can get about all the things that are wrong with the app,
アプリの問題部分の全容を 具体的にするほど―
the easier it will be to fix the problem because you'll have almost a task list
問題の修正がより簡単になります なぜなら 理想的な解決法が分かると―
on how to get to the ideal solution.
タスクリストをほぼ 手に入れたと言ってよいからです
Then after you've planned how you will attack the problem, go ahead and
問題への取り組み方を計画したら アプリ内で変更する点を―
implement those changes in your app.
実装していきましょう
Once the Order button works as expected, pat yourself on the back, and
「 Order 」ボタンの動作が予想通りになったら 自分自身をほめたたえて下さい
then check this box to continue.
そして 四角にチェックを入れて 次へどうぞ